http://www.virtualkiss.com/privacy.php

About UsAdvertisingPrivacy StatementAwardsPress MentionsHey Webmasters! Choose an Action------------------VirtualKiss.com Home------------------Send an e-KissCheck My HoroscopeRead Kissing StoriesGet Kissing TipsPlay a Kissing GameRead a Kissing ArticleEnter KissChatStickers!Who Did All This?------------------
VirtualKiss.com collects no personally identifying information about
our users, unless you knowingly provide that information.
Any personal information you provide, such as name, age,
location and personal preferences, is used for content purposes only.
If you don't want us to, or want us to stop using your personal
information in this way, send an email to the address below and let us
know.
When you voluntarily give out any personal information in chat areas,
that information can be collected and used by others.
They may send you messages that you don't want or that are
inappropriate. VirtualKiss.com suggests that you never post this type
of information in chat rooms, or other areas open to the public, for your
own safety.
If you are under 13 years of age you are not allowed to submit personal
information to this site. This is in compliance with the
Children's Online Privacy
Protection Act of 1998.
If you are 13-17 years old and you decide to post or send personal information to
us or to other areas on the Internet, you need to have permission from your
parents.
IP information is collected and is used to anaylize traffic on our site.
This information is for our use only and is never distributed to any third
party.
If you have any questions, you can email us at
info@VirtualKiss.com.
VirtualKiss.com works with a third party that serves ads to this site.
Third Party AdvertisingWe use DoubleClick's Network, Sonar, and other third-partyadvertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site.These companies may use information (not including your name,address, email address or telephone number) about your visits tothis and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on thissite and other sites about goods and services that may be ofinterest to you. If you would like more information about thispractice and to know your choices about not having this informationused by these companies, click herehttp://www.sonar.com/naiprivacy.Third Party CookiesIn the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-partyadvertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on yourbrowser. You can immediately opt-out of Doubleclick's unique cookies andhave it switched to a non-unique cookie by clicking herehttp://www.doubleclick.net/cgi-bin3/optout/check2.pl. You will have to repeat this process if your cookies get deleted oryou move to a new computer. More information on opting out ofDoubleclick's cookies can be found athttp://www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy/privacy.htm.
Click here to send this page to a friend!VirtualKiss.com - THE Online Kissing Resource!™kissing home | e-kiss™ |kissing tips | kissing stories |polls |boards | kissing quizzese-valentine | e-shamrock | kissing school | kissing games |astrology | kissing chronicleslip prints | chat |spycam | kissing contests | trunk o' fun links | gear | about us | contact us | advertiseAll content © 1996-2019 VirtualKiss.com, all rights reserved
